trumpinitiative.com 2010-06-07

# Privacy - The Trump Entrepreneur Initiative

Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to secure any information that you provide. Additionally, we exercise great care in providing safe transmission of your information from your PC to our servers (unless sent by a means outside of our control, such as e-mail).

Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our sites. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, you can contact us here.

#### How We Protect Your Personal information

We may request personal identification information from you (such as your name, street address, telephone number, credit card number, e-mail address, and/or any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of you) in connection with your use of, or participation in, membership registration, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, or additional information (including via email to us), and in connection with other activities, services or resources we make available on any of our sites. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Except as otherwise provided in this policy, we will never intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user to any third party without having received your permission.

If you do provide us with personal information for any of these activities, we may use it to conduct the activity. We may also use cookie technology (discussed in detail below) to improve your experience of these activities, including to remember your preferences, customize the content and advertisements that you see or authenticate your access to your personal information. In addition, in the event your personally identifiable information is requested as part of our surveys or polls, such personally identifiable information may be added to your registration information).

We may use your personal data in the following ways:

  * For the purpose for which you specifically provided the personal data, for example to enroll you in one of our courses, to process your order of one of our books or other materials, or to respond to a specific inquiry;
  * To send surveys or questionnaires so that we can learn more about our customers' needs and interests;
  * Unless you opt out, to send you our online newsletter, "Trump Insider Newsletter".
  * Unless you opt out, to send you information about new products or services that we think might interest you.

If you do not want us to send you surveys and questionnaires, or to provide you with information about our other products and services, you can opt out of receiving this information at any time.

We will release specific information about you or your account to comply with any valid legal inquiry or process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the Sites, or a physical or property threat to you or others. We may also transfer user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of related assets or corporate division or other fundamental corporate change.

Further, the information you enter when making a purchase will be shared with payment processors, financial gateways, and your credit card company to authorize credit card payments. Such information may also be shared with necessary third parties solely for the purpose or carrying out the transactions.

Please note that if you give out personal information online -- for example, on one of our public forums such as a message board or chat room, folder, chat IM feature -- that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users' privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you post in these forums. You disclose such information at your own risk.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use information     (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your information and password. You shall be responsible for all uses of your registration, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your registration or password.

#### How We Protect Your Billing Information

When you order from us online, we protect your information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. We are secured by GeoTrust, a leading provider of SSL encryption keys. SSL encryption electronically masks any information you send us. With this state-of-the-art system, you can enter your credit card number and delivery and billing information safely. The encryption process protects the information by scrambling it before it is sent to us. You can verify our compliance at any time by clicking on the GeoTrust logo located on our Shopping Cart page.

#### How We Use Cookies

We collect non-personal identification information through the use of cookies. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. We never sell or distribute cookie-based information. When you first visit www.trumpinitiative.com, we send a cookie to your machine to uniquely identify your browser. This allows us to identify your session across page requests, which we do to make your visit more effective. You may access the site without having cookies enabled, but cookies are required to log in. In addition, we may set other cookies to help us analyze site traffic; these cookies help us improve the site, and contain no personal user information.

#### Consent to Transfer

The Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Web Site, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

#### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes. Last Updated 11/10/06
